morning
today's the 5th of april 2010
i'm just demonstrating uh repulsion in
my
magnets which are pretty normal um
everybody says they they repulse
and i've just got a slight problem with
this one is that where it attracts
and holds on that repulsion
and fires away
all right you saw it here first on
youtube
thanks
i should be singing your tune but anyway
that's it
magnets
can
can hold down
or
that's what it looks like there you go
so yeah they repulse uh no they don't
they attract no they don't they repulse
all right there's a cheeky bastard
telling you about this
all right so what do you reckon
magnetics something to learn something
different to learn
that's what we're all about